Benjamin Cyna

0430653816 • Adelaide, SA • benjamincyna@gmail.com

My Portfolio • LinkedIn • Github

https://bit.ly/3h8GUFI • https://bit.ly/3aKr9lN • https://bit.ly/3g[1WMh

SUMMARY

Full-stack *software developer* with excellent organisational skills, self-reliant and independent with strong critical and logical thinking as showcased throughout my undergraduate degree in psychology, neuroscience and computer science. With a certificate in full-stack web-development, multiple certificates from udemy academies, contributions to open-soruce projects and experience working as a software developer, there are multiple roles that suit my qualifications. The utilisation of personal attributes such as ambition and creativity alongside good critical and logical thinking ensure engagement and quality in software creation.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, JavaScript, PHP,, C++, React, Laravel, | Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB | Tools: Git, Heroku, AWS, Laravel forge

PROJECTS

Code Noob Mar. 2021 - April. 2021

Group Project | https://github.com/bencyna/codeNoob | https://code-noob.herokuapp.com/

- Developed a responsive full-stack forum for people who want to get into coding without any prior experience.
- Used handlebars, user, home and API routes to retrieve and send information from front to back end
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS, handlebars, express, Bulma, sequelize, mySQL, bcrypt, uuid

Calendule Mar. 2021 - April. 2021

Individual Project | https://github.com/bencyna/calendule | https://calendule.herokuapp.com/

- Developed full-stack react app from scratch utilising sequelize, express and multiple npm packages
- Navigated MySQL to store user and event information with front and backend communication to display data
- Designed Front End functionality for a mobile responsive calendar app incorporating bootstrap.
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS, REACT, express, Bootstrap, sequelize, MySQL, bcrypt, uuid, @materials-ui

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

July. 2021 - Present

James Anthony Consulting | Adelaide, SA

- Lead developer of laravel admin system learning and utilising PHP/Laravel with my strong foundation in JavaScript
- Actively engaged in internal and client-facing meetings, adapting code to meet client demands
- Maintenance and bug fixing of old projects in C# and Java. Sole developer generating CSV and XML reports.

Tutor July. 2020 - July 2021

Tutoring For Excellence | Adelaide, SA

- Deriving explanations for complex tasks lead to a high rate of knowledge transfer from the educator to the mentee.
- Developed keen personal and social skills, requiring patience, critical thinking, understanding and effective communication within small groups.
- Maintained a 100% student retention rate across 5 students
- Increased student grades across all dimensions, including 3 final grade A+ results

EDUCATION

University of Adelaide | Certificate in Web-Development

Completed June 2021

University of Adelaide | Bachelor of Psychological Science 50% of Neuroscience major, 50% of Computer Science major

Expected July. 2022

• GPA: 6.8/7.0